fanporfan.es 2017-10-13

# Privacy Policy

The protection of your personal data is one of the concerns of FanporFan in its relationship with customers and third parties. In order to preserve and guarantee at all times your privacy, and in compliance with what is established in the Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13, of the Protection of Personal Data (“LOPD”), FanforFan informs you that, by completing the registration form and accepting it, by clicking the registration button in www.fanporfan.es, your personal data will be incorporated and processed in files owned by FanporFan, which, for legal purposes, is identified as responsible for them.

The User must full the registration form entirely. Otherwise, FanporFan will not be able to provide the services offered in the Portal. In particular, in order to operate in the on-line store, the User must also provide personal data that is indicated on the registration form for this purpose. The User declares that all information provided for the access to this Portal and while its using it, is true, complete, accurate, and you undertake to keep it up to date. FanporFan informs you that the collection of your personal data is produced by the following purposes:

  1. To be able to provide the services which you will have access through our Portal, a description of which is found in the General Conditions of Use of the same, that every User must visualize.

  2. For commercial and advertising of FanporFan products, as well as companies in its business group, regarding products, services, offers, promotions and any other advertising activities.

  3. To conduct surveys, statistics and analysis of market trends. For the latter, FanporFan also informs you that our server may send cookie files to your computer, which will allow us to know you better as a user and to personalize in the future, in this way and in your interest, the information through our Portal. In any case, you have the possibility of set your computer to refuse the installation of such cookies.

In compliance with the provisions of the LOPD, the User expressly authorizes FanporFan, to communicate the personal data to suppliers with whom FanporFan, reach commercial agreements, with the purpose of which they use them exclusively for the fulfillment of the contracted services and purposes.

This authorization is revocable at any time without retroactive effect.

We also inform to the User that the personal data relating to physicals persons collected in any of the sections of the Website, or any other provided by the User throughout the relation with FanporFan, as well as those collected as the result of the relation established, will be included in files of personal data owned by FanporFan.

This file will include the necessary data to provide the services that the users request as well as for communications from FanporFan.

The treatment is also intended to send you information about goods and services that may be of your interest, to expand and improve our services by adapting our website to your preferences or needs, to design new products and services and to send the questionnaires by any means, which reply is voluntary, unless otherwise is dictated.

The forms that may exists on the web, such as registrations, may have fields marked with an “asterisk” (*), those are obligatory, and failure to complete these fields may prevent the User from enjoying, totally or partially, the Services and information offered by the Website.

FanporFan will use your personal data for the following purposes:

  1. To open and manage a user account in your name, so that you can make use of all the functions of our services, including, but not limited to, make income in your user account, participate in the contests and make the purchases that you want.

  2. To have the possibility of receive your questions or comments through our Customer Service, by email.

  3. To confirm compliance with security rules and regulation of online contests, including the verification of age, as well as legal requirements and processes regarding fair play.

  4. In the event that you give your prior approval, inform you about future promotions and other FanporFan activities, as well as those communications related to the use of the service, such as regulatory changes or technical updates.

  5. For those additional uses necessary to ensure compliance with our contractual obligations to you.

Also, through the provision of your data, the interested party expressly authorizes FanporFan to send you information by email, in compliance with Article 21 of the Law 34/2002, July 11th, of Services of the Information of the Society and the Electronic Commerce (LSSICE).

In compliance with the rules of data protection, at any time the user may exercise their right of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition by contacting soporte@fanporfan.es using the same email address with which your communication was registered or sent.
